(Raj:)Wait, my laptop.
[HOWARD SIGHS]
Yeah, there's a point
when this becomes idiotic.
(Leonard:)And it wasn't
when we were driving like this?
(Sheldon:)I would advise the three of you
that resistance is futile.
(Sheldon:)I have endless patience.
I spent two and a half hours on hold
with Hewlett-Packard customer service...
(Sheldon:)...just to complain
about their customer service.
LEONARD:
You wanna talk about endless patience?
(Leonard:)Penny made me watch all five seasons
of Sex and the City.
RAJESH:
There's six seasons, dude.
LEONARD:
Oh, crap.
(Raj:)No, no, no, the sixth season is great.
(Raj:)We go to Paris with Carrie
and get our heart broken...
(Raj:)...and then Mr. Big shows up.
We don't know if we can trust him again.